{
    "translations": {
      "en": {
        "fa1": "../../../AV/VisFormalLang/NFA/AutomataFiles/NFA2DFA2a.jff",
        "q1": {
          "type": "multiple",
          "src": "../../../AV/Development/formal_language/FAEditor.html",
          "description": "A set is a collection of distinguishable members or elements. There is no concept of duplication in a set.",
          "question": "[T/F]Sets may contain duplicate elements.",
          "answer": ["False"],
          "choices": ["True", "False"]
        },
        "q2": {
          "type": "multiple",
          "src": "../../../AV/Development/formal_language/FAEditor.html",
          "description": "A set is a collection of distinguishable members or elements. There is no concept of duplication in a set.",
          "question": "Let $P = \\{7,11,42\\}$, Which of the following is correct?",
          "answer": ["$P = \\{11, 42, 7\\}$"],
          "choices": ["$P = \\{11, 42, 7\\}$", "$P  ≠ \\{11, 42, 7\\}$"]
        },
        "q3": {
          "type": "multiple",
          "description": "Set members are typically drawn from some larger population known as the base type",
          "question": "Let $P = \\{7, 11, 42\\}$, what is the base type of $P$ elements?",
          "answer": ["$Integers$"],
          "choices": ["$Integers$", "$Real$ $numbers$"]
        },
        "q4": {
          "type": "select",
          "description": "Each member of a set is either a primitive element of the base type or is a set itself.",
          "question": "Let $P = \\{a, b, c, \\{d, e\\}, \\{f\\}\\}$. Which of the followings are an element in the set.",
          "answer": ["$a$","$b$","$c$","$\\{d, e\\}$","$\\{f\\}$"],
          "choices": ["$a$","$b$", "$c$", "$d$", "$e$","$\\{d\\}$","$\\{d, e\\}$","$f$","$\\{f\\}$"]
        },
        "q5": {
          "type": "multiple",
          "description": "Sets common symbols: a) $\\{\\}$: braces that surround the set elements.",
          "question": "Which of the following is a valid set?",
          "answer": "$\\{a, 2, 3\\}$",
          "choices": ["$1$, $2$, $3$", "$\\{a, 2, 3\\}$"]
        },
        "q6": {
          "type": "multiple",
          "description": "Sets common symbols: b) $\\{x|x\\ is\\ a\\ positive\\ integer\\}$: A set definition using a set format",
          "question": "Choose what best explain previous set.",
          "answer": "positive integers",
          "choices": ["integers","negative integers","positive integers"]
        },
        "q7": {
          "type": "select",
          "description": "Sets common symbols: c) $x∈P$: $x$ is a member of set $P$ d) $x∉P$: $x$ is not a member of set $P$",
          "question": "Let $P = \\{a, b, c\\}$, which of the following is $∉P$?",
          "answer": ["$\\{a\\}$", "$\\{a, b, c\\}$"],
          "choices": ["$a$", "$\\{a\\}$", "$b$", "$\\{a, b, c\\}$"]
        },
        "q8": {
          "type": "multiple",
          "description": "Sets common symbols: e) ∅: The null or empty set",
          "question": "Which of the following is $∈Q$?",
          "answer": "$a$",
          "choices": ["$a$", "$1$", "$\\{a,b\\}$", "$Q\\ has\\ no\\ elements\\ because\\ it\\ is\\ the\\ null\\ set.$"]
        },
        "q9": {
          "type": "multiple",
          "description": "Set's common symbols: f) $|P|$: Cardinality: the size of set $P$ or number of members for set $P$",
          "question": "What does it mean to say that $|P|$ = $3$?",
          "answer": "P has 3 elements",
          "choices": ["P has 3 elements","P is 3","P has element 3"]
        },
        "q10": {
          "type": "select",
          "description": "Sets common symbols: g) $P⊆Q$, $Q⊇P$: Set $P$ is included in set $Q$, set $P$ is a subset of set $Q$, or set $Q$ is a superset of the set $P$",
          "question": "Let $P = \\{x|x\\ is\\ a\\ positive\\ integer\\}$. Which of the following is a subset of $P$?",
          "answer": ["$\\{1, 2, 3\\}$", "$\\{x|x\\ is\\ an\\ even\\ number\\}$", "$\\{x|x\\ is\\ a\\ prime\\ number\\}$"],
          "choices": ["$\\{1, 2, 3\\}$", "$\\{x|x\\ is\\ an\\ even\\ number\\}$", "$\\{x|x\\ is\\ a\\ real\\ number\\}$", "$\\{x|x\\ is\\ a\\ prime\\ number\\}$"]
        },
        "q11": {
          "type": "multiple",
          "description": "Sets common symbols: i) $P∪Q$:  Union: all elements appearing in $P$ OR $Q$",
          "question": "Let $P = \\{1, 3, 5\\}$, and $Q = \\{2, 4, 5, 6\\}$ What is $P∪Q$?",
          "answer": "$\\{1,2,3,4,5,6\\}$",
          "choices": ["$\\{1,2,3,4,5,6\\}$", "$\\{1,3,5\\}$", "$\\{2,4,5,6\\}$", "$\\{5\\}$"]
        },
        "q12": {
          "type": "multiple",
          "description": "Sets common symbols: i) $P∪Q$:  Union: all elements appearing in $P$ OR $Q$",
          "question": "Let $P = \\{1, 3, 5\\}$, and $Q = \\{2, 4, 5, 6\\}$ What is $Q∪P$?",
          "answer": "${\\1,2,3,4,5,6\\}$",
          "choices": ["$\\{\\}$","$\\{1,2,3,4,5,6\\}$"]
        },
        "q13": {
          "type": "multiple",
          "description": "Sets common symbol: i) $P∪Q$:  Union: all elements appearing in $P$ OR $Q$",
          "question": "Select the correct fact about set union",
          "answer": "$P∪Q$ = $Q∪P$",
          "choices": [
            "$P∪Q$ = $Q∪P$",
            "$P∪Q$ ≠ $Q∪P$"
          ]
        },
        "q14": {
          "type": "multiple",
          "description": "Sets common symbols: j) $P∩Q$: Intersection: all elements appearing in $P$ AND $Q$",
          "question": "Let $P = \\{1, 3, 5\\}$, and $Q = \\{2, 4, 5, 6\\}$ What is P∩Q?",
          "answer": "$\\{5\\}$",
          "choices": ["$\\{1,2,3,4,5,6\\}$","$\\{1,3,5\\}$","$\\{2,4,5,6\\}$","$\\{5\\}$"]
        },
        "q15": {
          "type": "multiple",
          "description": "Sets common symbols: j) $P∩Q$: Intersection: all elements appearing in $P$ AND $Q$",
          "question": "Let $P = \\{1, 3, 5\\}$, and $Q = \\{2, 4, 5, 6\\}$. What is $P∩Q$",
          "answer": "$\\{5\\}$",
          "choices": ["$\\{1,2,3,4,5,6\\}$","$\\{1,3,5\\}$","$\\{2,4,5,6\\}$","$\\{5\\}$"]
        },
        "q16": {
          "type": "multiple",
          "description": "Sets common symbols: i) $P∩Q$:  Intersection: all elements appearing in $P$ AND $Q$",
          "question": "Select the correct fact about set union",
          "answer": "$P∩Q$ = $Q∩P$",
          "choices": ["$P∩Q$ = $Q∩P$", "$P∩Q$ ≠ $Q∩P$"]
        },
        "q17": {
          "type": "multiple",
          "description": "Sets common symbols: k) $P$ $-$ $Q$: difference: all elements of set $P$ NOT in set $Q$",
          "question": "Let $P = \\{1, 3, 5\\}$, and $Q = \\{2, 4, 5, 6\\}$ What is $P-Q$?",
          "answer": "$\\{1,3\\}$",
          "choices": ["$\\{1,3\\}$","$\\{1,3,5\\}$","$\\{2,3,5,6\\}$","$\\{2,4,6\\}$","$\\{1,2,3,4,6\\}$"]
        },
        "q18": {
          "type": "multiple",
          "description": "Sets common symbols: k) $P$ $-$ $Q$: difference: all elements of set $P$ NOT in set $Q$",
          "question": "Let $P$ = $\\{1, 3, 5\\}$, and $Q = \\{2, 4, 5, 6\\}$ What is $Q-P?$",
          "answer": " {2, 4, 6}"
        },
        "q19": {
          "type": "multiple",
          "description": "Sets common symbols: k) $P$ $-$ $Q$: difference: all elements of set $P$ NOT in set $Q$",
          "question": " Select the correct fact about the set difference:",
          "answer": "$P-Q$ ≠ $Q - P$",
          "choices": ["$P-Q$ = $Q - P$", "$P-Q$ ≠ $Q - P$"]
        },
        "q20": {
          "type": "multiple",
          "description": "Sets common symbols: k) $P$ $x$ $Q$: Set (Cartesian) Product: yields a set of ordered pairs",
          "question": "Let $P = \\{1, 3, 5\\}$, and $Q = \\{2, 4\\}$ What is $PxQ$?",
          "answer": "$\\{(1,2),(1,4),(3,2),(3,4),(5,2),(5,4)\\}$",
          "choices": ["$\\{(1,2),(1,4)\\}$", "$\\{(1,2),(1,4),(3,2)\\}$","$\\{(1,4),(3,2),(5,2),(5,4)\\}$","$\\{(1,2),(1,4),(3,2),(3,4),(5,2),(5,4)\\}$"]
        },
        "q21": {
          "type": "multiple",
          "description": "Sets common symbols: k) $P$ $x$ $Q$: Set (Cartesian) Product: yields a set of ordered pairs",
          "question": "Let $P = \\{1, 3, 5\\}$, and $Q = \\{2, 4\\}$ What is $|PxQ|$?",
          "answer": "6",
          "choices": ["3","4", "5","6", "7"]
        },
        "q22": {
          "type": "multiple",
          "description": "The powerset of a set $S$ (denoted $2S$ ) is the set of all possible subsets for $S$",
          "question": " Consider the set $S = \\{a,b,c\\}$. What is $2^S$?",
          "answer": "$\\{∅, ${a}$, ${b}$, ${c}$, ${a,b}$, ${a,c}$, ${b,c}$, ${a,b,c}$\\}$",
          "choices": ["$\\{∅\\}$","$\\{∅, ${a}$, ${b}$, ${c}$, ${a,b}$, ${a,c}$, ${b,c}$, ${a,b,c}$\\}$","$\\{∅, ${a}$, ${b}$, ${c}$\\}$","$\\{∅, ${a}$, ${b}$, ${c}$, ${a,b}$, ${a,c}$\\}$"]
        }
      }
    }
  }
  